<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Recipes on Byzantine Kitchen</title>
    <link>https://byzantinekitchen.github.io/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Recipes on Byzantine Kitchen</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2017 12:00:00 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://byzantinekitchen.github.io/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Halloumi Paprika</title>
      <link>https://byzantinekitchen.github.io/post/halloumipaprika/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2020 05:04:46 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://byzantinekitchen.github.io/post/halloumipaprika/</guid>
      <description>Difficulty: very easy Time: 10 minutes Ingredients (6 people):  Halloumi (225g)  Seasoning:  Paprika (more than one type if available) Thyme Pepper Cayenne pepper (optional) Olive oil  Instructions: Cut the halloumi into small slices. In a big pan heat some olive oil, then place the halloumi slices in the pan, add pepper and paprika. Fry until golden on one side then turn and add more seasoning. Add thyme to finish with.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Red Lentils and Poached Eggs</title>
      <link>https://byzantinekitchen.github.io/post/renlentils/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2020 21:04:46 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://byzantinekitchen.github.io/post/renlentils/</guid>
      <description>Difficulty: very easy Time: 20 minutes Ingredients (4 people):  Red Lentils (250g) Onion (1) Tomatoes (200g) Mascarpone (125g) Garlic (couple of cloves) Eggs (4) Parsley Hard Cheese Olive oil Salt and Pepper White Wine Venegar  Optional:  Garden Peas (150g) Butternut Squash (150g) Truffle oil  Instructions: Pre heat oven at 200 degree celsius. Cut the tomatoes in half, place in a baking tray, add olive oil salt and pepper.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Strawberry and Chocolate Desert</title>
      <link>https://byzantinekitchen.github.io/post/strawberrychocolate/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2020 21:04:46 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://byzantinekitchen.github.io/post/strawberrychocolate/</guid>
      <description>Difficulty: very easy Time: 5 minutes Ingredients (4 people):  Skyr strawberry (450g) Mascarpone (200g) Ground almonds (50g) Strawberry (200g) Raspberries (100g) Dark chocolate (25g)  Instructions: Mix the Skyr, ground almonds and mascarpone together. Serve in big bowls. Cut the strawberry in half and add on top of the mix with raspberries. Put the chocolate in a small bowl with water and put in the microwave for several seconds until the chocolate is melted.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mango Salad</title>
      <link>https://byzantinekitchen.github.io/post/mangosalad/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Dec 2019 21:04:46 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://byzantinekitchen.github.io/post/mangosalad/</guid>
      <description>Difficulty: very easy Time: 15 minutes Ingredients (6 people):  4 Mangoes 2 Cucumbers 2 Red peppers 5x400g Canned Chickpeas Coriander  Seasoning:  1 Lime White Wine Vinegar (or similar) Hemp oil, Olive oil (or similar) Salt Chili (powdered or chopped)  Instructions: Peel and cut the mangoes and cucumbers into small pieces. Cut the red peppers into small pieces.
Add the chickpeas, seasoning and chopped coriander, mix everything.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quinoa Salad</title>
      <link>https://byzantinekitchen.github.io/post/quinoasalad/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2019 21:04:46 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://byzantinekitchen.github.io/post/quinoasalad/</guid>
      <description>Difficulty: very easy Time: 25 mins Ingredients (6 persons):  Quinoa (500g) Kale (80g) 4 apples Sweet peppers (300g) 5 spring onions Canned chickpeas (240g) Cranberries (150g) walnut to taste  Seasoning:  1 lemon Mustard (1 full tsp) White Vinegar (2 tsp) Balsamic Vinegar (1 tsp) Hemp oil (2 tsp)  Instructions: Cook the quinoa in vegetable stock.
Wash and cut the sweet peppers, apples, spring onions and kale in small pieces.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>